alright guys welcome back to another video and in this tutorial I want to
好吧欢迎回到另一个人 视频和我想要的本教程
show you guys how to do some basic transformations on your image and by
告诉 你们如何做一些基本的 在图像上，并通过变换
transformation I mean things like resize flip rotate um like stretch so let's go ahead and get started and I think I'm
转换我的意思是调整大小 翻转旋转，就像伸展一样，让我们​​走吧 提前开始 ，我 想我是
going to use this picture me as a baby for this tutorial so I'll name it baby
打算把这张 照片用作婴儿 对于本教程，我将其命名为 baby
baby bulky image open baby JPEG and let's just go ahead and show this first
婴儿笨重的图像打开婴儿 JPEG 和 让我们先行先展示一下
so baby show alright so let's see what we're starting with so this is the basic image that we're going to be
所以宝贝表现 得好，让我们看看是什么 我们开始这样，这 是 基本的 我们将成为的形象
manipulating and the first transformation I want to show you guys
操纵和第一个 转型我想告诉你们
is just how to resize it so let me actually see so the image size of this
只是如何调整其大小，所以让我 实际上看到这个的图像大小
is 450 by 341 let's say we were making like a website or something or just a piece of software and we want it to take
让我们说我们正在 制造 450到341 像一个网站或什么或只是一个 一块软件，我们希望 它采取
an image and make it square so fit perfectly in our profile now what we can
一个图像，使其正方形 如此合适 完全在我们的个人资料中 我们能够做到
do is actually cut out a square from somewhere in the middle in order to show
实际上切出了 一个正方形 中间的某个位置， 以 示
you guys how to cut it but if you just want to pretty much take the image and
你们怎么 削减它， 但如果你只是 想要几乎采取图像和
resize it into a square this is what you do just name this square baby and I'll
将它调整为正方形 这 就是你 只要这个方形婴儿命名，我会
set this equal to baby which is your original file your original photo and
设置这等于宝贝，这是你的 原始文件 您的原始照片和
the function is called resize and what it does is it takes a tupple so make sure you add these double
该函数被调用 调整大小，它需要做什么 tupple所以请确保添加这些双倍
parentheses right here this these outside ones are for the function
括号这里就是 这些 外面的是为了这个功能
parameters in these inside ones is pretty much the tupple itself and the
这些内部的参数是 很多人都是这样的
tupple is of course just the size that you want to resize it to so i want to
tupple当然只是那个尺寸 你想调整 它 ，所以 我想
take that original image and resize 250 by 250 so now the square baby if we show
采取 原始图像和调整 250 如果我们展示的话现在是方形宝贝 250
it check it out so that was our original one and this is our resize the baby
它检查出来， 这是 我们原来的 一个，这是我们调整宝宝的大小
Bucky square baby so that is how you accomplish that now another thing I want to show you guys is what if you want to
Bucky square baby 这样就是你 现在完成我想要的另一件事 如果你愿意，告诉你们这些人是什么
flip it upside down or flip it you horizontally or vertically well let's
将它 翻转或翻转你 水平或垂直放好吧
name this one flip baby and in order to do this of course take your original
将此名称翻转为婴儿并以此为准 这样做 当然 要拿你原来的
baby object in the function is actually called transpose and this is actually
实际上婴儿对象的功能 叫转置，这实际上是
the you use the same function whether you want to flip it or rotate it so what
在您使用相同的功能是否 你想翻转它还是旋转 它
you can do is you can um call this property of actually I wonder if it pops
你能做的就是你可以这么称呼它 实际上我不知道它是否会 弹出
up yep so flip left right and flip top bottom are two different ways that you
高达没错所以翻转 左 ，右和翻盖 底部是 你的 两种 不同 方式
can flip it of course left to right along the axis in top bottom this is
可以翻转它当然是从左到右 沿着顶部底部的轴线，这是
pretty much vertical and horizontal probably would be easier if it said that
几乎垂直和水平 如果 这样说可能会更容易
actually I think I like left to right top bottom better so pretty much take
实际上 我觉得我喜欢从左到右 顶部的 底部更好， 所以非常需要
the left and put it where the right is pretty simple so now if we show flip
左边，把它放在右边 非常简单，所以如果我们显示翻转
baby we can see I have three different transformations that was our original
宝贝我们可以看到我有三种 不同 转换是我们 原来的
one that was a square one and this is the flip baby now remember I flipped it
一个是方形的，这是 翻盖的宝贝现在还记得我翻过 它
left and right so that's why it didn't flip upside down that would be top
左，右， 这就是为什么没有 翻转颠倒，这将是 顶部
bottom left to right means pretty much just flip it along that axis we just
从左到右从左到右意味着相当多 我们只是沿着那个轴翻转它
close all these is getting kind of messy in the last one I want to show you guys
关闭所有这些都变得有点混乱 在最后一个我想 告诉 你的家伙
is this might as well type it out so you can do spin baby and what this does is if you call baby transpose you can call
是不是这样打字就可以了 可以做旋转宝宝，这是做什么的 如果你打电话给婴儿 转置你可以打电话
image dot rotate now as you can see as soon as I type R we have a couple of
图像点现在旋转，你可以看到 我输入R时，我们有几个
properties that pop up rotate 180 270 and 90 so let me just go ahead and
弹出的属性旋转180 270 90所以让我先走一步 ，
rotate it 90 degrees actually if we rotated this image 180 degrees think
旋转它 实际上90度 ，如果我们 将此图像旋转180度思考
about what it does it pretty much just takes in flips it upside down so it
关于它的作用几乎就是这样 把它颠倒翻转所以它
cheeves the same effect is flip top bottom but if we just rotate it in 90
cheeves同样的效果是翻盖 底部，但如果我们只是旋转它90
degrees then show you guys what it does right here
度，然后告诉你们它做了什么 就在这儿
it'll look like it's on its side pretty much so let's run all those again check
看起来它看起来很漂亮 所以让我们再次检查所有这些
it out original one square flipped and rotated pretty sweet so those are just some real quick simple transformations
原来一个方形翻转了 旋转得很甜，所以那些只是 一些真正快速简单的转换
and I suppose square run Oh interesting but anyways there you go again to square
而且 我想方形 跑哦有趣 但无论如何，你再去广场
it up it's resize and for your other transformations you use the transpose
它为你的另一个调整大小 您使用转置的转换
class or excuse me the function so well there you go in the next tutorial I'm
或者请原谅我 这个功能 在那里你进入下一个教程我
going to be showing you guys how to convert one image mode to another image
将向你们展示如何做到 将一种图像模式转换为另一种图像
bone it's going to be sweet so I'll see you then
骨头它会变甜，所以我会看到 然后你